pwspoilers.com 2010-12-31

# Privacy Policy - PWSpoilers.com

Power Web Spoilers (PWSpoilers.com) has developed the following privacy policy to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. All information below represents the privacy policies followed by PWSpoilers.com

PWSpoilers.com is a site open to general audiences and all site-content is filtered (where possible) to ensure the privacy of users remains intact, and the site remains appropriate for all audiences.

On a general basis, any information sent to PWSpoilers.com will be kept private and stored securely. PWSpoilers.com will never sell, rent, loan, trade, lease, or freely distribute any personal information collected.

**Advertisements:**  
PWSpoilers.com serves ads for an array of different sponsors and third-party organizations. Such advertisements are not developed or monitored by the PWSpoilers.com staff and may collect information about users’ visits (not including name, address, telephone number and e-mail address – unless the user voluntarily submits such information to the advertiser). No advertisements fall under the PWSpoilers.com privacy policy, therefore exempting PWS from any issues with such advertisers.

**Cookies:**  
PWSpoilers.com does not use any cookies to collect information from users, although any future discussion forums that could be added to the site in the future use cookies to make navigation easier for users, depending on their choices during registration. Third-party advertisers, as well, may use cookies, but such advertisers do not fall under the terms of this privacy policy.<p>

**External Links:**  
In the course of one’s visit to PWSpoilers.com, he/she may have the opportunity to click a link and be taken to a third-party website. PWSpoilers.com is in no way associated with such websites and is not responsible for their privacy practices and policies.

**Policies for Children:**  
PWSpoilers.com understands that children under thirteen have very special and important privacy needs.

We will not knowingly collect and/or distribute any personal, identifiable information from children without parental consent.

We will not knowingly store the e-mail addresses of children for contact, that extends past a one-time response to an inquiry made by a child.

We will not entice or give children an incentive to submit more information than is needed to access a feature of this website.

Any first-party links to content that may be inappropriate for children will be labeled as such in age-appropriate terms. Third-party links, as mentioned above, are not under the jurisdiction of this policy.

We, as often as possible, will encourage children to get parental consent before submitting information to the website.<p>

**E-Mail Lists:**  
At a certain point in time, PWSpoilers.com may develop an e-mail list, in which specialized sports content will be delivered to one’s e-mail inbox. No visitors will be forced to receive such information and no personal data will be collected from those who opt-in to our list.

**Contests/Giveaways:**  
PWSpoilers.com may, from time to time, have contests or giveaways. In such a case, users will have the complete choice of entering such an event, and if so, will then have to submit personal information, used in transferring of prizes. No personal information will be used for any other purposes.

**Questions/Concerns:**  
Anyone who has a question regarding the privacy practices of PWSpoilers.com should submit an inquiry to webmaster@pwspoilers.com
